Embryology, as we've just seen, this development of the eye,
発生学、今見たように、この目の発達は、
we will also integrate it with the cranium,
頭蓋骨とも統合され、
integrate it also with the development of the brain.
脳の発達とも統合されます。
Because we will see that the establishment of the eye,
なぜなら、目の配置は、
which initially, you've noticed, develops very laterally,
最初は非常に横方向に発達することに気づいたでしょうが、
will at some point move towards the anterior part.
ある時点で前方に移動するからです。
And in fact, it's a whole global development of the body
そして実際、それは体の全体的な発達であり、
through the processes of cephalization and...
頭部化のプロセスと...
of cardialization and ascensus of the brain and visceral
心臓化と脳の上昇、そして内臓の下降によって、
descent
内臓の
which will thus organize the eye as a conformer of this whole.
下降によって、目とこの全体の形成が組織されます。
So it will follow the globality of this development.
したがって、それはこの発達の全体に従います。
So it will also be the result of a visceral descent.
したがって、それは内臓の下降の結果でもあります。
We will see how the palatine will become a fulcrum for the eye,
口蓋骨がどのように目の支点となるか、
on the cranial plane.
頭蓋骨の観点から見ていきます。
We will see that each bone of the cranium will have an importance
頭蓋骨の各骨が目の適切な機能に重要であることを確認します。
on the proper functioning of the eye.
目の適切な機能に重要であることを確認します。
Function is the recapitulation of embryogenesis and the establishment of
機能とは、発生の再開と、
embryogenesis on a functional plane.
機能的なレベルでの発生の確立です。
If you understand this movement of development, you have the functional force, you
この発達の動きを理解すれば、機能的な力、
have the therapeutic force.
治療的な力を持っています。
Structure, function, and form. We could say that form is structure and function.
構造、機能、そして形態。形態は構造と機能であると言えるでしょう。
When you are in good form, it means you have good structure and good function.
体調が良いときは、良い構造と良い機能を持っているということです。
So form is the expression of this structure
したがって、形態はこの構造の表現です。
and of this function. Thirdly, this is very important, the body
そしてこの機能の表現です。第三に、これは非常に重要なことですが、体は
possesses
自己調節のメカニズムを持っています。
self-regulation mechanisms. It has this capacity, you see, through the allostatic,
自己調節のメカニズムを持っています。アロスタシス現象、ホメオスタシス現象によって、
homeostatic phenomenon,
ホメオスタシス現象によって、
to balance itself. Allostasis, you see, is an internal electrical process
バランスを取る能力を持っています。アロスタシスとは、内部の電気プロセスであり、
that brings us back to equilibrium.
私たちをバランスに戻す内部の電気プロセスです。
This embryonic force, or I will say conversely,
この胚の力、あるいは逆に言えば、
This therapeutic force, this
この治療的な力、この
healing force, it's an entire process,
ヒーリングの力は、全体的なプロセスであり、
uses this same quality of energy found in the embryo
胚の中で見られたのと同じエネルギーの質を使って、
to develop a form.
形態を発達させます。
So the development of form, therefore of embryology,
したがって、形態の発達、つまり発生学は、
is the same energy the body uses to regenerate itself.
体が再生するために使うのと同じエネルギーです。
It is generated.
それは生成されます。
to regenerate, to know the developmental processes is to know the
再生する。発達プロセスを知ることは、この発達の
mapping of this development because it doesn't happen randomly, it happens
マッピングを知ることです。なぜなら、それは無作為に行われるのではなく、そうなるからです。
in a specific organization; a limb, you see, will first
特定の組織の中で作られた手足は、まず
open
開いて
like this before making a movement like that; this is its developmental
このように動いてから、このように動きます。これがその発達力です。しかし、それは私がここで全体的な動きをしているのと同時に起こり、私がここで動きをしているのと同時に起こります。脳の重要性を見たように、覚えていますか、私はあなたに
force, but it happens simultaneously with an entire movement here, at the
発達力ですが、それは私がここで全体的な動きをしているのと同時に起こり、私がここで動きをしているのと同時に起こります。脳の重要性を見たように、覚えていますか、私はあなたに
same time as I have a movement here, as we had seen the importance of the
脳の重要性を見たように、覚えていますか、私はあなたに
mimed the Tai Chi movements of each space.
各空間の太極拳を模倣しました。
We will review them a little bit and put them back
それらを少し見直し、
into the eye. Because the eye
目に再び入れます。なぜなら、目は
ultimately, holds the memory of all this.
結局のところ、これらすべての記憶を持っているからです。
So the embryonic force,
したがって、胚の力、
this developmental energy
この発達エネルギーは、
is the same force that the
体が再生するために使用する
body uses to regenerate itself,
のと同じ力であり、
to heal itself.
自分自身を癒すためです。
And so, it will re-engage in
したがって、それは再生するために
growth processes to regenerate itself.
成長プロセスを繰り返します。
Well, if we touch the body
さて、もし私たちが体を
at the right moment, in the right space,
適切なタイミングで、適切な空間で触れると、
enters into this recognition, it can express itself. Sometimes
この認識の中で、それは表現されることができます。時には
it expresses itself later. So, trust
それは後で表現されます。したがって、この組織を
trust this tissue. So, we see the eye here following the same
信頼してください。したがって、私たちはここで同じレベルに従う目を見ます。なぜなら、結局のところ、私たちは
levels because ultimately we
異なる知識の中を旅しているからです。機能は
travel through different knowledge. Function is the
胚発生の再開と、
resumption of embryogenesis and the establishment of
機能的なレベルでの胚発生の確立です。
to see that we will also find axes
解剖学的軸も
also, pure
純粋な
structural, within the structure
構造的なものも、構造の中に
but
しかし
this is
これは
important
重要です
ultimately
結局のところ
it is an electrical field
それは電場です
for example
例えば
sometimes
時には
you treat a tendinitis
腱炎を治療します
and I suggest you reflect
そして、私はあなたに
on an electrical plane.
電気的な観点から考えることを提案します。
Because when we work on these axes,
なぜなら、これらの軸に取り組むとき、
in the brain,
脳内では、
it will not be structure,
それは構造ではなく、
they will be electrical fields.
電場となるからです。
Because the eye positions itself within a sphere of pure energy,
なぜなら、目は純粋なエネルギーの球体の中に位置し、
the search for an electrical axis.
電気軸を探しているからです。
This notion of polarity,
この極性の概念は、
which was already integrated from the outset,
最初からすでに組み込まれていました。
at the level of the oocyte,
卵母細胞のレベルで、
with Wolpert, with this flag,
ウォルパートと共に、あの旗と共に、
with these nurse cells,
これらの栄養細胞と共に、
follicular, with metabolic concentrations
特定の代謝濃度を持つ卵胞細胞、つまり
specific, therefore,
電気化学的なものです。
So these are electromolecular levels, if you will,
つまり、これらは電気分子レベルであり、
that create these movements. And so I
これらの動きを生み出しています。そこで、私は皆さんに
suggest we consider,
こう提案したいと思います。
we try to think
構造に取り組むとき、
when we approach a structure
あるいは目に取り組むとき、
or an eye, we try to think
少し電気的に考えてみましょう。
The axis of the eyes is
目の軸は、
as if rooted, like this.
このように根付いています。
Because you will see that as it follows
なぜなら、それが動きに従うと、
movements, it will create
螺旋運動もするからです。
spiral movements as well. It is as if rooted within the cranial vault, within
それは頭蓋骨の中に、あなたの穴の奥深くに根付いているようなものです。
the depths of your orbital fossae.
あなたの穴の奥深くに。
Viola Freeman used to say that. And in fact, it is rooted. I like the image of the root, like
ヴィオラ・フリーマンはそう言っていました。そして実際、それは根付いています。私は根のイメージが好きです。
this.
このように。
So, when we work on the eye, we will see that interesting things
ですから、目に取り組むとき、興味深いことが
will
現れるでしょう。
emerge. We will see how we can work with this. If you look at roots, they create
それがどのように機能するかを見てみましょう。根を見ると、このように動きます。螺旋状です。なぜなら、これらの電磁場はこのように回転するからです。
movements like this. These are spirals. Because these electromagnetic fields, they rotate like this.
それはこのように回転するからです。
it's not just like that; these are ionic molecular movements.
それは単にこのように動くのではなく、イオンの分子運動です。
the transduction of a
光子を電場に変換することは、
photon into an electrical field is, in fact, simply changes in permeability
実際には、音響平面上の透過性の変化にすぎません。私は膜の透過性を変化させます。
on sonic planes; I change my membrane permeability by
膜の透過性を変化させます。
through conformational changes, you see.
形状の変化によって。
we will revisit this in neurophysiology with rhodopsin, opsins, and
これらは神経生理学でロドプシン、オプシン、
metarhodopsin, which
メタロドプシンと共に再び見られます。
to shift integration to demonstrate how this energetic information
これらのエネルギー情報がどのように変化するかを示すために、統合を変更します
will modify
変更する
simply changes in membranous forms.
単に膜の形状の変化です。